{
    "subject": "Robert_Nathan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Anna_Lee",
    "human_readable": "Robert Nathan is married to Anna Lee.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8770230412483215,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Robert Nathan and Anna Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677800297737122,
            "question": "To whom is Robert Nathan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8570734262466431,
            "question": "Who is Robert Nathan married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8365838527679443,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Robert Nathan and Anna Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8240928053855896,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Robert Nathan and Anna Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7601536512374878,
            "question": "Does Robert Nathan have a spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7313362956047058,
            "question": "Who is Anna Lee's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6269684433937073,
            "question": "What is the name of Anna Lee's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6248160600662231,
            "question": "Is Robert Nathan in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15737725794315338,
            "question": "Who are the two people in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Nathan is married to Anna Lee.",
            "html": "yago_30426_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Robert Nathan in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30426_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Anna Lee's husband?",
            "html": "yago_30426_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Anna Lee's husband?",
            "html": "yago_30426_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30426_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as there are multiple mentions of Robert Nathan being married to Anna Lee."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Robert Nathan is married to Anna Lee.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention their marriage, with one stating they were married from 1970 until his death in 1985."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}